[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Mr. Trump, can I call you Donald finally?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Trump", ",", "can", "I", "call", "you", "Donald", "finally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "You certainly may.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "certainly", "may", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Trump", "Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What is your reaction to that breaking news?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "breaking", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, I know a lot of politicians and I can tell you that they're not so different from this guy other than they don't do it on Facebook or whatever he was doing it on, and there's a lot of affairs going on in Congress.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "a", "lot", "of", "politicians", "and", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "so", "different", "from", "this", "guy", "other", "than", "they", "do", "n't", "do", "it", "on", "Facebook", "or", "whatever", "he", "was", "doing", "it", "on", ",", "and", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "affairs", "going", "on", "in", "Congress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "If I was honest I certainly was.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "honest", "I", "certainly", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["25 percent"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What are the top priorities for President Trump?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "top", "priorities", "for", "President", "Trump", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, I think the first thing I'd do is announce very strongly that we're going to tax Chinese products, 25 percent tax on all Chinese products.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "first", "thing", "I", "'d", "do", "is", "announce", "very", "strongly", "that", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "tax", "Chinese", "products", ",", "25", "percent", "tax", "on", "all", "Chinese", "products", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "ORGAN: You see them as the enemy, don't you, Donald?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "see", "them", "as", "the", "enemy", ",", "do", "n't", "you", ",", "Donald", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I see them as the enemy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "them", "as", "the", "enemy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you think we have smart enough people to deal with the Chinese and the Indians and these new competitors out there in business?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "we", "have", "smart", "enough", "people", "to", "deal", "with", "the", "Chinese", "and", "the", "Indians", "and", "these", "new", "competitors", "out", "there", "in", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I think they're smart but I don't think they have any savvy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "smart", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "have", "any", "savvy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Can't we work with them?", "question_tokens": ["Ca", "n't", "we", "work", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I don't think they're friends.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "'re", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And don't we just need more people like you to compete with them?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "n't", "we", "just", "need", "more", "people", "like", "you", "to", "compete", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "You need to have people that know how to deal with the Chinese.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "need", "to", "have", "people", "that", "know", "how", "to", "deal", "with", "the", "Chinese", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "How did you get this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "A woman reached out to us.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "woman", "reached", "out", "to", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Are you taken aback by the speed of his resignation?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "taken", "aback", "by", "the", "speed", "of", "his", "resignation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Do you feel sorry for him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "sorry", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I've never heard of anybody -- well, you feel sorry for the person but this was really ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "heard", "of", "anybody", "--", "well", ",", "you", "feel", "sorry", "for", "the", "person", "but", "this", "was", "really", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Is he more a question for you than just a bad judgment rather than the morality of it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "more", "a", "question", "for", "you", "than", "just", "a", "bad", "judgment", "rather", "than", "the", "morality", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, it's morality but it's also bad judgment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "morality", "but", "it", "'s", "also", "bad", "judgment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Would you fire a senior employee at your company for a similar thing?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "fire", "a", "senior", "employee", "at", "your", "company", "for", "a", "similar", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "If he's married and starts sending pictures of himself.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "he", "'s", "married", "and", "starts", "sending", "pictures", "of", "himself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Do you still feel that was the wrong way around, that perhaps we get our priorities wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "feel", "that", "was", "the", "wrong", "way", "around", ",", "that", "perhaps", "we", "get", "our", "priorities", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "RUMP: Well, I thought -- I'm a Republican.", "answer_tokens": ["RUMP", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "thought", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "Republican", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What is your -- what is your view of President Obama right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "--", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "President", "Obama", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think he's a nice man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "nice", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "But is this the problem?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "this", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "But we'll see what happens.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "we", "'ll", "see", "what", "happens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Who is leading the Republicans and who should be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "leading", "the", "Republicans", "and", "who", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I don't think there is a leader right now of the candidates.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "is", "a", "leader", "right", "now", "of", "the", "candidates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Is this -- is this precisely why you're so tempted to run?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "--", "is", "this", "precisely", "why", "you", "'re", "so", "tempted", "to", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I am tempted to run, but I think the primary reason I'm tempted -- I guess, yes, I think I could win, otherwise I wouldn't do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "am", "tempted", "to", "run", ",", "but", "I", "think", "the", "primary", "reason", "I", "'m", "tempted", "--", "I", "guess", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "think", "I", "could", "win", ",", "otherwise", "I", "would", "n't", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Defensive?", "question_tokens": ["Defensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 449, "question": "If you were president would you take all American troops out of Afghanistan and Iraq now?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "president", "would", "you", "take", "all", "American", "troops", "out", "of", "Afghanistan", "and", "Iraq", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Saudi", "Saudi Arabia"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "MD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, it's interesting, Saudi, as I mentioned to you tonight, the other breaking news is that the king of Saudi Arabia has been very firm with President Obama basically telling him to leave off Mubarak.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "Saudi", ",", "as", "I", "mentioned", "to", "you", "tonight", ",", "the", "other", "breaking", "news", "is", "that", "the", "king", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "has", "been", "very", "firm", "with", "President", "Obama", "basically", "telling", "him", "to", "leave", "off", "Mubarak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "And so, what do you think of that situation as it's developing where you're beginning to see the old order in the Middle East standing up to America and saying, this is our business not yours?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "situation", "as", "it", "'s", "developing", "where", "you", "'re", "beginning", "to", "see", "the", "old", "order", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "standing", "up", "to", "America", "and", "saying", ",", "this", "is", "our", "business", "not", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "They're standing up for the first time because they don't respect us anymore.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "standing", "up", "for", "the", "first", "time", "because", "they", "do", "n't", "respect", "us", "anymore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General Motors", "Coca-Cola"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "They do?", "question_tokens": ["They", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Companies like General Motors, companies like Coca-Cola.", "answer_tokens": ["Companies", "like", "General", "Motors", ",", "companies", "like", "Coca-Cola", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Isn't that what you would do instinctively?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "what", "you", "would", "do", "instinctively", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I think it's great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "What was wrong with the system here that should now be put right properly?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "wrong", "with", "the", "system", "here", "that", "should", "now", "be", "put", "right", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Look, you've always going to have problems with financial systems.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "you", "'ve", "always", "going", "to", "have", "problems", "with", "financial", "systems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chase"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Should bankers -- the same bankers that got us into the mess now be allowed, in a regulation way, to be awarding themselves huge bonuses?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "bankers", "--", "the", "same", "bankers", "that", "got", "us", "into", "the", "mess", "now", "be", "allowed", ",", "in", "a", "regulation", "way", ",", "to", "be", "awarding", "themselves", "huge", "bonuses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Look what happened with Chase today.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "what", "happened", "with", "Chase", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What do they want you to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "want", "you", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "They want me to say Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "want", "me", "to", "say", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Is that your steely philosophy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "steely", "philosophy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Not everybody can think big.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "everybody", "can", "think", "big", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Have you?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "You don't even drink coffee, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "even", "drink", "coffee", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "And I don't drink coffee.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "do", "n't", "drink", "coffee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Women are your vice, right?", "question_tokens": ["Women", "are", "your", "vice", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I respect women.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "respect", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Do they follow your lead?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "follow", "your", "lead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "So far, my kids have been following my lead.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "far", ",", "my", "kids", "have", "been", "following", "my", "lead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Even though he hated the taste to start with?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "though", "he", "hated", "the", "taste", "to", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "He hated the taste.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "hated", "the", "taste", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "There's a banker -- and obviously I'm not going to mention names.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "banker", "--", "and", "obviously", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "mention", "names", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Is he still a senior banker?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "a", "senior", "banker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "He just retired.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "just", "retired", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "You lost respect for him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "lost", "respect", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "RUMP: I lost respect for him.", "answer_tokens": ["RUMP", ":", "I", "lost", "respect", "for", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "What's the secret?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Well, I guess it's my looks.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "it", "'s", "my", "looks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "What's more important to you, women or business?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "more", "important", "to", "you", ",", "women", "or", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Well, business is more important because I'm a happily married man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "business", "is", "more", "important", "because", "I", "'m", "a", "happily", "married", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "With my wife?", "question_tokens": ["With", "my", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Would that include my wife?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "include", "my", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "What kind of husband have you been, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "husband", "have", "you", "been", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Well, I think I've been a very good husband lately.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "'ve", "been", "a", "very", "good", "husband", "lately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "Are you vain?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "vain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "I think I am pretty vain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "am", "pretty", "vain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "What is the look?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "Well, it's a lot different looks.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "different", "looks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "ORGAN: If I want the look, what is it?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "If", "I", "want", "the", "look", ",", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Well, you've got a long way to go.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'ve", "got", "a", "long", "way", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "So it's all real, but it's probably the most famous hair in America, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "all", "real", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "probably", "the", "most", "famous", "hair", "in", "America", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "Well, I guess it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "Are they demeaning to women, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "demeaning", "to", "women", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "How tough a dad are you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "tough", "a", "dad", "are", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Pretty tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "If one of -- it would have to be Ivanka in your case -- had gone off the rails like Lindsay Lohan has gone off the rails, how would you deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "one", "of", "--", "it", "would", "have", "to", "be", "Ivanka", "in", "your", "case", "--", "had", "gone", "off", "the", "rails", "like", "Lindsay", "Lohan", "has", "gone", "off", "the", "rails", ",", "how", "would", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "That's a very tough thing.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "tough", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lindsay Lohan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 908, "question": "Are you ready to put it behind you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ready", "to", "put", "it", "behind", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 909, "answer": "I heard she had some very nice things to say.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "heard", "she", "had", "some", "very", "nice", "things", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "Are you ever going to retire?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ever", "going", "to", "retire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]